And send Me the children ….
Fate venire i bambini ....
Now come along, wash My Feet.
Venite qui, lavate i miei piedi.
Come along, both of you, come along.
Venite, tutti e due, venite.
Now put up your sleeves first of all,
Rimboccate le maniche prima di tutto,
put up your sleeves properly. Good.
Rimboccate bene le maniche. Bene.
Both the hands.
Entrambe le mani.
Salutations to the one who incarnates as the past.
[Yogi: Omaggio a colui che si incarna come passato.
Bhuta bhava.
Bhuta bhava.]
All the left side. He’s at the base of the left side,
Tutto il lato sinistro. Lui è alla base del lato sinistro,
so you’ll understand what is he telling.
così capirete cosa sta dicendo.
He’s the left side, the past.
È il lato sinistro, il passato.
“Bhuta” is “past.”
“Bhuta” è “passato”.
No, ... you first say the meaning.
No, ... prima dici il significato.
Then you say this, so they will understand;
Poi dici questo, così capiranno;
it goes into the head, all right? The first is the meaning.
entrerà in testa, d’accordo? Prima il significato.
Now, second one you say.
Ora, leggi il secondo.
“Bhuta sangha” means the collection of all that is created.
“Bhuta sangha”, la raccolta di tutto ciò che è stato creato.
“Bhuta sanghana videha manah”:
“Bhuta sanghana Videha Manah”:
“videha” means “ in the body”,
“Videha” significa “nel corpo”,
“manah” means “in the heart of that body,” in Sanskrit.
“Manah” significa “nel cuore di tale organismo”, in sanscrito.
… In the heart.
... nel cuore.
“Bhutatmanaha”. Atmana is the Spirit.
“Bhutatmanaha”. Atmana è lo Spirito.
“Bhut” means “created”: whatever is created,
“Bhut” significa “creato”: tutto ciò che è stato creato,
He resides them as the Spirit.
Risiede come Spirito.
“Bhutatmanaha.”
“Bhutatmanaha”.
Now here I would like to say that it is Shri Ganesha
Ora qui vorrei dire che è Shri Ganesha
who is the Omkara, who is the vibrations.
che è l'Omkara, le vibrazioni.
So He is the truth. What He says is the truth,
Egli è la verità. Quello che dice è la verità
so, what vibrations say is the truth.
per cui, ciò che dicono le vibrazioni è la verità.
He's truth.
Lui è la verità.
So Omkara is vibrations, that is Shri Ganesh.
L'Omkara rappresenta le vibrazioni, e cioè Shri Ganesha.
“Paramadhama”.
“Paramadhama”.
Too much. Too much.
Troppo. Troppo.
Better take one with ….
Meglio prendere uno con ....
Now, you have to tie up those ….
Ora, bisogna legare quei .... [Hindi]
Let them take photograph.
Fagli fare una fotografia.
Now, can you come?
Ora puoi venire?
Be careful.
Fai attenzione.
Can you tie?
Puoi legarlo?
Did you avoid in the photograph these things? Did you avoid?
Hai evitato di fotografare queste cose? Hai evitato...
...showing?
... di mostrarle?
No, no, take it out, that one.
No, no, tienilo fuori, quello.
It’s a good photograph, all right?
È una buona fotografia, va bene?
So that it’s a formidable photograph.
In modo da renderla una fotografia formidabile ....
with the head of Shri Ganesha.
con la testa di Shri Ganesha.
May God bless you all.
Che Dio vi benedica tutti.
Oh God...Wow, beautiful. Thank you.
Oh Dio ... Oh, bellissimo. Grazie.
From the italian sahaja yogis.
Dai Sahaja Yogi italiani.
It is too much for Me. Thank you very much.
È troppo per me. Grazie mille.
What is that?
Cos'è questo?
Wow, beautiful! Very nice. From where did you get it?
Oh, bellissimo! Molto carino. Da dove l'avete preso?
Oh, I see, is very good.
Oh, vedo, è molto buono.
What is this? She's come from Austria all the way?
Cos'è questo? È venuta fin qui dall'Austria?
… Ah! From Austria! Thank you very much ….
... Ah! Dall'Austria! Molte grazie ....
Thank you very much. How beautiful it is. Very beautiful.
Grazie mille. Come è bello. Molto bello.
Thank you very much.
Molte grazie.